{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "You ________ speak more clearly. I don't understand anything.",
            "a": "ought ",
            "b": "can't",
            "c": "should ",
            "d": "may",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Excuse me, _______ I smoke in this room?",
            "a": "may ",
            "b": "shall",
            "c": "ought ",
            "d": "should",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "When my daughter got married, she _______ cook.",
            "a": "might not ",
            "b": "couldn't",
            "c": "oughtn't ",
            "d": "shouldn't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The noise they made was deafening. You _______ have heard it.",
            "a": "ought ",
            "b": "mightn't",
            "c": "mustn't ",
            "d": "must",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You _______ say such words in front of the children. It's disgusting!",
            "a": "mightn't ",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "oughtn't ",
            "d": "couldn't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I _______ lend you some money, if you promised to return it.",
            "a": "might ",
            "b": "can",
            "c": "ought ",
            "d": "should",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You _______ heard the explosion. It was deafening.",
            "a": "might ",
            "b": "might have",
            "c": "could have ",
            "d": "must have",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is still there. You ________ hurry.",
            "a": "might not ",
            "b": "shouldn't",
            "c": "oughtn't ",
            "d": "needn't",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He _______ be Old Jim, Old Jim is dead.",
            "a": "wouldn't ",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "can't ",
            "d": "hasn't",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think we _______ to write about that subject yet. It's too sensitive.",
            "a": "should ",
            "b": "must",
            "c": "ought ",
            "d": "might",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "9",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}